The application begins with a landing page that introduces its purpose and features. Users can log in to access their respective dashboards tailored for admin, doctor, or patient roles.
Admins can add new users by filling out a form. Once created, the system sends an email with temporary credentials to the new user.
Admins have the ability to trigger emergency alerts for patients. This simulates critical health scenarios and tests the alerting workflow.
Admins can edit user details, such as display name, contact email, and role-specific information, directly from the admin dashboard.
When a patient logs in for the first time, they are prompted to set a new password, ensuring secure access to their account.
The patient dashboard provides an overview of health metrics, a profile page for managing personal details, and access to other patient-specific features.
The doctor dashboard displays a list of assigned patients, their risk levels, and tools for managing care plans, medications, and health data.
Doctors can review and approve AI-generated care plans, ensuring they align with the patient’s needs.
The medication management tab allows doctors to add, edit, or delete medications for their patients, ensuring accurate treatment plans.
The messaging tab enables doctors to communicate with their patients. This feature supports real-time chat for better interaction.
Doctors can suggest medications and monitor adherence. Notifications alert patients about missed doses, ensuring timely medication intake.
Patients receive test messages and notifications from their doctors, keeping them informed about their health and treatment.
Patients can report symptoms categorized as mild, moderate, or severe. The system analyzes these reports, sends emergency emails for severe cases, and intelligently handles moderate conditions.
AI analyzes health trends to provide insights and actionable recommendations for doctors, enhancing patient care.